In this episode where we our team is red our team is playing against Richard and
We have a problem where we play so defensively all the time and we're not proactively attacking
So we're just defending wave after wave and that's our policy. Yes, these in the defensive position and then you know wait to defend
defense but then never ends up attacking and that's a problem. You see we're
defending not really doing anything that much. Yeah we don't know where the
enemy is but we're not proactively going at or sending a player out. We need
to do so and then this keeps happening even though we defend very well not
attacking so we're not winning. Okay so this keeps happening and then we keep defending wave
wave after wave from blue. Okay but then at the end of the end of...
Towards the end of the game, how does Blue end up winning?
Well, they charge, and they have one Ranger character left.
See, this, or this character right over here,
this character single-handily takes down us the tower
and all of our other characters.
And so we have to avoid this happening,
because this is why we end up losing.
So we need to figure out why this Ranger is so good.
as good.